I'm not wearing latex yet, but this is going to be a latex video because AlienHarness from Ukraine sent me two latex outfits and a latex cat hood, which I'm going to show you.
Often I'm wearing the outfits in my videos for the very first time, but in this case it was a bit different.
Last week I met up with the wonderful Selina to take some pictures at a city harbor and I've worn one outfit and she's worn the other outfit.
I can show you some clips from that day because we did not only take pictures but also made some videos. And my outfit is a dress which is bust free so I'm wearing a triangle bra together with the dress so it's a full outfit and that way I can show it to you now and I'm not nude.
and she was wearing the two-piece set a jacket a crop jacket and a penny with a zipper
and I think they look really cool together my dress is orange which is really unusual for me
I think it was the first time I've ever worn orange latex but I thought hey it's probably
going to look good with my blue hair and I have to say it did and I also wore the matching heels
or at least I thought they were matching because the orange was a bit too bright for the latex
orange. It was super hot that day like 30 degree and we were outside in the evening at seven o'clock
and we were still sweating like hell because yeah latex and warm weather what else do I need to say
everyone who knows latex knows that you're melting if you're wearing it in that temperatures. So I've
worn the orange combination but since I did not wear the other two-piece set yet that's what I'm
going to show you now. This is the two-piece set as promised and I love how versatile it is. You
could also wear the panty with the triangle bra or use the top for another leggings or maybe pair
with the jeans and normal clothes. So this is the version with the zipper open. Of course I can also
close it. Well, like that. This is 0.4 millimeter gauge, standard size or standard thickness rather
and we have a zipper in the panty that is all the way from the front to the back which makes it
really easy to put it on and get out of as well as with this zipper in the jacket. I love that
It makes dressing latex so much easier if there's a zipper
This is a two-piece set at the moment
But I think there's a cool hack to make this a one-piece set which I'm going to show you
Because I have a little corset I can add to this
Tada! Now it looks like a bodysuit one piece, which is also really cool and since it's a corset, what am I going to add?
Of course a steel belt
That way you can upgrade every look really easily.
I think it matches super well together with this silver zipper.
Let me turn around again.
I promised you a latex catsuit in the beginning and here it is.
So if you wanna have like the full fit experience you can of course add a hood to the outfit
which makes a completely different look again.
I think this one is really cute because of the cat ears here which flap around really
funnily and it has a zipper in the back which again matches the jacket and is also easy
to put on. If you want to see even more hoods and more latex outfits check out
Alien Harness online they also make leather harnesses. Like I said a small
Ukrainian brand I'll link everything in the description text down below and if
you have any questions leave a comment. Thanks to Alien Harness for working with
me and I hope you here enjoyed the video, the pictures and also the outdoor videos. Let me know
in the comments if you would like to see more outdoor videos and that was it for today. Leave
a thumbs up and subscribe to my channel, check out my Patreon. See you in the next video, have a nice day, bye!
She sings me the saddest of songs
I cannot help but sing along
Forever after in my head
There'll be no stopping once she starts
The eternal burden of the queen of my heart
I wanna be free, I can't let go
She doesn't really know why
I feel so tired
By the way, if you want to know more about Selina, check out her channels. I'll link them below.